Hm...
[Sighs]
They sent you, huh?
New York.
Maybe you have
a bigger brain
than my boss.
I'll tell you,
five years, five years
I'm saying,
Very dangerous Lafferty.
Fuckers.
They're evil danger.
But nobody listen, never.
They don't take serious, yeah?
They say Šváb is crazy.
Šváb is too old,
you know.
Splashing on his lighthouse.
And now,
pretty lady doctor.
She's not so
pretty anymore.
But now everybody listen.
Now they say,
Šváb, maybe you're
not so crazy
Šváb, work with
an agent, America.
James Bond.
It's wasting
time and money.
But okay,
I cooperate.
We say here,
For every pig
there's boiling water.
And you will help me
with boiling Lafferty.
You want coffee?
Automat outside.
[Swears in Czech]
Yeah.
Here, we make for you.
Papers about dead lady.
Autopsy report,
what she's buying
and who she's calling.
But look,
I can save your time.
One month ago,
Same house,
same room.
They killed cat.
They make fire ritual
symbol around it.
Terrible.
I like cats.
And now,
they kill doctor.
Same place.
Same symbol.
Aha!
We say here,
with more food,
grow the taste.
what's next one, huh?
Nothing.
Next one...
That son of a bitch, we show
him prison, ha! Lafferty...
He will really meet
Satan!
[phone rings]
I hear you.
Understood, over.
They have him for us
in the bracelets!
Ugly fucker.
Now you can come
meet in person.
Mr. Devil.