Is that what I get
for all those love notes
I sent you, Šváb?
You fool.
You fucking stinking
ignorant rat.
Those remaining seven brain cells
that are rattling around
inside that
ugly head of yours
got the first clue
about the forces that
they're dealing with, hmm?
A life was taken
and you still...
Well,
I wonder
who'll be next.
Wonder I do.
[phone rings]
I told you not to call
me when I'm at work.
But I shouldn't be rude.
Not when we have such
distinguished company,
an overseas rat.
exactly what
we'd be missing, hmm?
But I kid,
Lucien Lafferty.
Pleased to make
your acquaintance.
You look tired.
Are you sleeping okay?
Yes, I'm the arch brother
of the brotherhood of Faust.
Don't be fooled,
we're no psychopath club
as the Švábs of this
world would have you believe.
Of course I understand,
to the uninitiated,
some of our
opinions and rituals
may seem rather frightening.
What frightens me
are the billions of lives
lived through compromise.
Silent desperation.
Our aim is to remind
people of life's basic alchemy.
The forest must
burn in order to grow in you.
Something must die so
that something may be born.
You know,
there's no coincidence
I set up here in
Prague, of all places.
This is the tip of
a magical triangle, yeah?
A place of remarkable access
to the most fundamental of forces.
Our rituals go back millennia.
Šváb's probably imagining
thousands of our
brothers worldwide, what?
lighting scented
candles and running a dagger
through the heart
of their pet ferret.
Of course that couldn't
be further from the truth.
I am the only one authorized
to conduct any form of ritual.
It's certainly
never just willy-nilly.
There is no
gain without sacrifice.
And rather than sacrifice,
our sovereignty, our soul,
you could just
see our brothers, huh?
They certainly aren't
angry and hunched over.
Ah! Finally we
get to the big question.
Where was I Friday night?
You want to
know if I'm responsible
for the death
of little Miss Doctor?
Well, that's for me to know.
For you to
find out, isn't it now?
But let me ask you this.
Hwo do you think the
Catholic Church would feel
if somebody turned
the Sistine Chapel
into a grocery store.
So keep on investigating, yeah?
Our numbers grow every day.
The longer we play, the
more the word of our cause spreads.
Oh, my glory!
Shut up already,
you bastard.