I'm usually the first one in
in the morning, sorry.
because I like
to finish early
to make visiting hours
at the hospice, my grandpa...
Anyway, yeah.
So...
I came upstairs and...
And there she was.
She looked so lifeless.
But maybe peaceful?
She looked...
Very calm,
you know?
I'm sorry.
I was working on restoring
the floor in the main library.
It got damaged
in the recent fire.
I'm sorry.
It's just such
a terrifying thing, you know.
One moment and then...
And she was
such a nice lady.
Beautiful.
Her office was that...
Well,
on that floor.
She'd always
bring coffee and...
she was interested
in my work.
Actually interested,
you know?
Not just to be polite.
I think,
maybe...
She was also running
away from that boss doctor.
I think
he's a little creepy.
You know?
Friday evening?
Oh...
I wasn't here at all.
I went to the mountains
right after work, to Beskydy.
In the East.
Almost on Polish
border, you know.
Oh...
I go most weekends.
I grew up there
with my grandpa.
I cut the grass
and take care
of the garden a bit...
Yeah...
He seems worried
about it so much.
He's so frail now.
They say
there's no cure.
Just some
experimental treatment.
That costs
a ton of money.
Money...
Such a silly thing when
you think about it, yeah?
And it could drive
a person crazy.