Pa, pa, pa, pa.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Where were we?
Yeah, well,
Dr. Mandl and I,
we had a professional
relationship.
I was naturally very pleased
when she reached
out like six months ago.
And then she expressed
her interest to join our ranks.
And she definitely made a
very valuable addition to our team.
Ugh, it's a...
We were really all
very shaken by what happened.
I spoke with her in
the afternoon the day, you know.
She was about
to take some time off,
and I just abode to
iron out some logistics.
That's truly a horrible thing.
And you can't imagine
the nightmare in
that all this is causing.
One-sided.
Well, this is rich.
Clearly you have seen
our private communications.
I actually see why
it might seem one-sided.
The truth
about Sarah is...
She was-
she wasn't what she seemed.
I did all
sort of favors for her.
She really wanted an
office in this Faust house,
so I made it happen.
Although I usually
try to keep our
doctors out of
this damn building.
To avoid more bullying
from those lunatics, you know.
And...
Good evening Mr. Doctor!
Evening, evening.
Well, as I said,
she was almost
a split personality.
You know...
Hot one day
and ice cold the other.
I thought maybe
she was teasing me.
You know?
These long, meaningful looks.
And all of a sudden,
cold shoulder
and making me out as...
Almost as some
stalker or something.
You know what?
I think this was
her nature.
To manipulate.
She was a manipulator,
right.
She... You know, she
played with everyone a game.
And you know what?
Maybe this
was also her own doing.
Oh my God.
Where was I friday.
At home, with my
wife, feel free to ask.
I mean, be mindful, though.
I would hate to hurt her.
But if you are now suspecting me,
let me save you some time.
The truth is,
and let's stay this between us.
The time off
Sara was taking,
we were supposed to go
together on a secret vacation.
She acted so aloof for
the longest period of time.
But the Friday I saw her,
she was back to her sweet self.
And she actually confirmed
we would meet the next day
on the airport.
And I mean, I was waiting
there almost all Saturday.
Sorry.
Yeah.
I'll be there when
the door opens.
If you're bored, walk up and
down the stairs, that won't harm you.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, I'm sorry.
I'll have to excuse me.
There is an
emergency board meeting.
So if you need
anything else, you have my number.