Yeah.
I sure thought
we were close.
We lived together
for seven years.
So yeah.
We could say we were close.
The fuck do I know.
Six months.
I've been trying
to have a phone call.
Conversation.
Fucking something.
And not even...
when I come out here.
Halfway across
the fucking world.
Then ring ring!
Look who's fucking calling.
I should have
fucking hated her by then.
But no.
I was just so happy...
to finally see her again.
I don't know
what I was expecting.
But...
Kind of merciless.
And impenetrable.
Fucking impenetrable
block of concrete.
Think you're worth it.
Oh shit.
Insurance policy.
What?
Oh ho ho ho ho.
That thing.
You mean...
the insult to the injury?
I found a way to pay you back.
Sure did.
Me.
Stupid cow.
I bought her...
a rare edition of Faust.
As a romantic gesture.
And she, very romantically,
pulls out some sort of...
insurance
policy for me to sign.
You know, there's some
poetry in there.
Somewhere.
You know, even when things
were really great between us...
there was always someone else.
Some other darling.
Head over heels she was.
Gambling.
Can you believe it?
Yeah.
So apparently...
it all started
when she was an intern.
All those long
nights at the hospital.
No.
She couldn't fucking
attend in like a normal person.
No, no, no.
No.
She had to
clickety-clack
on the computer late at
night in the kitchen.
All these weekends away
with friends I never heard of.
After a while, she
stopped trying to hide it and...
said she had a system.
Some fucking system.
She took out a loan
in my name, behind my back.
And I still forgave her!
I just asked her
to be honest with me.
But no.
She took a different route.
Didn't she?
Fucking Ice Queen.
She'd go to Prague.
Once, twice a year.
To see her grandma.
She's been living here
since the commies fucked off.
And gave them back
that apartment building,
that their family
used to have or something.
And this last
time I couldn't go.
Something must have happened.
Because when she came
back, she was all like, "Mmm."
And then a few days
later, a note on the nightstand.
"Sorry, I have to move
to Prague.
Don't come looking for me."
"Sorry?"
Fuck you!
I should have just moved on.
How do you do that?
So I did some
poking around.
I found out
she was working
in the same hospital
like her Czech
great-grandfather.
We've been there together
to see it a couple years ago.
Same building.
How could that?
[SIGH]
Friday?
Where was I
Friday night?
It's Friday, I'm in love.
Saturday!
Found a way to pay you back.
Kiss my ass like you do.
To die.
To sleep.
For chance to dream.