Yes, my father did
work in that godforsaken house.
He was head of
the hospital back then.
I was very little,
but I remember glimpses of it.
And it's no coincidence
that Sarah was at that house.
It was about half a year ago.
She came to visit.
I could tell right away
that something was very wrong.
It didn't take much prodding.
Apparently she
owed money, a lot of it,
to some very
scary people.
I told her not to worry.
"Move out here," I said. "Start
a fresh." "I'll settle all your debts.
I mean, what am I
going to do with all this?"
But she wouldn't have it.
She was a good girl at heart.
Hated seeing me sell my
inheritance to pay her debts.
But I could
tell it was serious.
And so I lost my
good sense, fool that I am.
"There may be
another way," I said.
"I held my tongue for decades,
but it was so hard
to see her suffer so
much good
did that to her."
My father was a
very successful man,
as was his father before him.
As the war drew nearer,
my parents only realized
they would have to flee
when it was almost too late.
It certainly wasn't possible
to get out any amount of wealth.
The noose had tightened.
We were lucky to
get out with our lives.
But my father
wasn't going to leave at all.
He bought up lots of gold.
People were
hiding their treasures
in the walls and
the cellars of their houses.
But my father
saw that wasn't safe,
and he came up with a plan.
"Hide it at the
hospital, in the Faust House."
So we fled,
first to London and
eventually to the States.
My father got a job
at a hospital in Connecticut,
and he never did get a
chance to go back for his wealth.
Towards the end
he was a man possessed.
"That's your wealth
hidden in that house," he said.
"Your future hidden
in that house," he said.
"Your future,
always the future."
Ambition.
I seem to be the only one
who doesn't have the obsession.
I half-forgot the story.
Something in me told me
I should take it to my grave,
as of course
I should have done.
After I told
Sara, she was changed.
Soon after,
moved out here
and got a job
in that house.
I comforted myself.
Thinking whatever
had been hidden there
would surely
long be gone.
She wouldn't find anything
and eventually come to
her senses and accept my offer.
But now I think...