You think life is full of surprises?
Don't even get me started on death.
Let me tell you about my
brilliant master plan.
But before you judge me
try to put yourself in my shoes:
a completely out of control gambling habit
i know you're telling me...
Yeah, so that;
the resulting mounting debt,
and one very questionable
Russian businessman.
And then I decided to run off with his money.
So,
when it came down to it, I could face
retribution
blackmail
shame
prison.
Or,
I could put it all on double zero.
Now, the problem was: how do you find an actual
treasure hidden inside
a huge hospital building?
So,
I warmed my way into having an office there
and got to work.
I studied blueprints,
got a precious metal detector...
Bottom line:
there was gold. A bunch of it, hidden
underneath the library floorboards.
But how do I get in there without raising
suspicion?
That's where crazy baldy came into play
with his absurd cult.
His whole
stunt with the media around arguing over
the Faust House was the perfect pretext.
I set fire to the library floor in the
shape of their little
"pentagram"
(the cat
was just a last minute addition.
I ran over the poor thing on my way there.
I figured it would add some flair.)
I don't even think that Lafferty guy even
knew I existed. He was
obviously not the one who killed me, he was
just some
snake oil salesman that could serve
as a good cover story.
So that was part one of the plan done.
Soon they started to work on the floors and
I was just waiting for my moment.
Part two was trickier, though.
I knew i'd never get Ivan off my back;
and if he got wind that I came into money,
the blackmail would only get worse.
So, I figured my only option was
to die.
That meant saying goodbye to my
sweet Elizabeth.
She-
she couldn't keep a secret for the life of her.
But i figured I could pay her back with
plenty of interest with the insurance policy!
My sweet Elizabeth.
she-
loved me.
Until the very end.
So, I figured to make my suicide more
believable, the heavy rains and
flooding made throwing myself in the river
a good option.
Nobody would be surprised that they
couldn't find my body.
But still-
I needed a good reason - a little
dramatic flair, you know, that pushed me over
the edge.
I felt a little bad for blaming
Chief Vykryl
I mean I did string him along
the entire time, but-
I didn't feel that bad.
That guy's a fucking creep.
So, I bought a fake passport
- surprisingly easy -
rented a van,
and and made a convincing suicide note.
Then i just waited for everyone
to go home for the weekend
Then I planned to take my time wheeling the
gold out in my suitcase.
Then I was off to Switzerland with their
excellent anonymous banking system.
Then that cop
Svab
started snooping around.
I just
I couldn't have him poking his nose in
unannounced to "investigate the crime scene"
for the hundredth time
So, I arranged a meeting with him at my office.
And just to think that was one of my last
experiences in life...
Anyway-
I thought that took care of everything.
Who could have known that earlier that day
while she was working on the floorboards
sweet, quiet little Eva
had stumbled into a gold bar.
When she came back for it
- all shaky, the poor dear -
I was in the middle of dinner.
I heard a noise.
And I saw her carrying a gold bar.
Just one.
Grandma always said, you know, my family was
cursed with greed. She said that that's what
killed my parents-
I don't know.
But in that moment I just
I couldn't let her have it.
Not even one.
We fought over it
for a while
and uh
then I saw it
in her eye.
I don't get scared that easily but I
knew to be scared then.
And in a split second she
changed
she pushed me.
And I mean what are the fucking odds...
But-
I just remember
warmth
and
quiet.
Finally.
And I remember her apologizing
over and over;
and I felt bad for her.
And I felt bad for myself.
It's funny, you know.
Dying can really solve a lot of your anger issues.
I can almost recommend it.